Guide to the R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company Archive 1844-2005
University of Chicago Library
- Series XV: Customers and Products
  - Subseries 1: Alphabetical Files
    - Remodeling, 1999 (Box 838, Folder 16)
    - Reno/ Tahoe Dining, undated (Box 838, Folder 17)
    - Renovator's Supply (Box 838, Folder 18)
    - Republican National Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 838, Folder 19)
    - Research, 1981 (Box 838, Folder 20)
    - Research Institute of America, 1984-1985 (Box 838, Folder 21)
    - Residential Architect, 1999 (Box 838, Folder 22)
    - Restaurant Business, 1976-1984 (Box 838, Folder 23)
    - Restaurant Hospitality, 1999 (Box 838, Folder 24)
    - Restaurant and Hotel Design, 1983-1988 (Box 838, Folder 25-26)
    - Retirement Life, 1984-1989 (Box 839, Folder 1)
    - Revolution, 2000 (Box 839, Folder 2)
    - Rice, 1988 (Box 839, Folder 3)
    - Richina Media Holdings, 1996 (Box 839, Folder 4)
    - Right On!, 1980s (Box 839, Folder 5)
    - Ring, 1990-1992 (Box 839, Folder 6)
    - Ripley, circa 1990s (Box 839, Folder 7)
    - Road Racer, 1988-1989 (Box 839, Folder 8)
    - Road & Track, 1959 (Box 839, Folder 9)
    - Roaman's, 1981-1985 (Box 839, Folder 10)
    - Robert Hall, 1976 (Box 839, Folder 11)
    - Robinson's, circa 1980s (Box 839, Folder 12)
    - Rock It, 1986 (Box 839, Folder 13)
    - Rodale Press, 1970-1987 (Box 839, Folder 14)
    - Roland Users Group, 1980s (Box 839, Folder 15)
    - Roller Skating, 1980 (Box 839, Folder 16)
    - Rosie, 2001 (Box 839, Folder 17-18)
    - Ross, circa 1980s (Box 839, Folder 19)
    - Ross-Simons, 1988-1992 (Box 839, Folder 20)
    - Rotary International, 1929-1986 (Box 839, Folder 21)
    - Row, Peterson, and Company, 1936 (Box 839, Folder 22)
    - Royal Silk, 1989 (Box 839, Folder 23)
    - Rubbermaid, 1979 (Box 839, Folder 24)
    - Rue de France, 1987-1991 (Box 839, Folder 25)
    - Runner, 1978-1987 (Box 839, Folder 26-27)
    - Runner's World, 1979-2001 (Box 839, Folder 28-34)
    - Running, 1980 (Box 840, Folder 1)
    - Russell Performance Producers, 1985-1986 (Box 840, Folder 2)
    - Rytex, 1991 (Box 840, Folder 3)
    - S9, 1976-1979 (Box 840, Folder 4)
    - Saga International Holidays, 1988-1992 (Box 840, Folder 5)
    - Sail, 1973-2000 (Box 840, Folder 6-12)
    - Sailing World, 1989-1992 (Box 840, Folder 13)
    - Sweetwater Sportsman, 1979-1989 (Box 840, Folder 14-18)
    - Sam's Club, circa 1990s (Box 840, Folder 19)
    - Samsco, 1954 (Box 840, Folder 20)
    - Samuel Robert Direct, 1990-1991 (Box 840, Folder 21)
    - San Diego Magazine, 1988-2001 (Box 840, Folder 22-23)
    - Sara Lee, 1989 (Box 840, Folder 24)
    - Sassy, 1991 (Box 840, Folder 25)
    - Satellite TV, 1983 (Box 840, Folder 26)
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1981-1987 (Box 841, Folder 1)
    - Savvy, undated (Box 841, Folder 2)
    - Saxitone Audio/Video, 1987 (Box 841, Folder 3)
    - Scan Line Office Interiors, circa 1980s (Box 841, Folder 4)
    - Schuck's Auto Supply, circa 1980s (Box 841, Folder 5)
    - Science Digest, 1979-1992 (Box 841, Folder 6-9)
    - Sciences and Nature, 1992 (Box 841, Folder 10)
    - Scientific American, 1964-1998 (Box 841, Folder 11-17)
    - Score Board, 1988-1989 (Box 841, Folder 18)
    - Scottish and Irish Imports, 1986 (Box 841, Folder 19)
    - Scottish Quest, 1986-1991 (Box 841, Folder 20)
    - Screw Machine Supply Company, 1934 (Box 841, Folder 21)
    - Scripture Press Publications, 1987 (Box 841, Folder 22)
    - Sea, 1987 (Box 841, Folder 23)
    - Sears, 1993 (Box 841, Folder 24)
    - Sebastian, circa 1980s (Box 841, Folder 25)
    - Second Wind, 1988 (Box 841, Folder 26)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1955 (Box 841, Folder 27)
    - Security Pacific, 1987 (Box 841, Folder 28)
    - Seifert's, circa 1980s (Box 841, Folder 29)
    - Selective Software, 1990-1991 (Box 841, Folder 30)
    - September Days, 1983 (Box 841, Folder 31)
    - Service Merchandise, circa 1990s (Box 841, Folder 32-33)
    - Service Merchandise, 1996 (Box 842, Folder 1)
    - Sesame Street, 1979-1990 (Box 842, Folder 2-4)
    - Seton Name Plate Corporation, 1987-1988 (Box 842, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Avenue, circa 1980s (Box 842, Folder 6)
    - SF, 1989-1990 (Box 842, Folder 7)
    - SGF, 1987-1988 (Box 842, Folder 8)
    - S&H Green Stamps,1968-1978 (Box 842, Folder 9)
    - Shannon, 1979-1980 (Box 842, Folder 10)
    - Sharper Image, 1991 (Box 842, Folder 11)
    - Shaw Walker & Co., 1961 (Box 842, Folder 12)
    - Sharson Lehman Brothers Andy Williams Open, 1987 (Box 842, Folder 13)
    - Shell, 1968-1979 (Box 842, Folder 14)
    - Shelter, 1991 (Box 842, Folder 15)
    - Sheplers, 1988-1999 (Box 842, Folder 16)
    - Shining Star Publicatoins, 1987-1989 (Box 842, Folder 17)
    - Shirtique, 1986 (Box 842, Folder 18)
    - Shop Rite, 1991 (Box 842, Folder 19)
    - Shoppers Advantage, 1991 (Box 842, Folder 20)
    - Shopping News, 1933 (Box 842, Folder 21)
    - Show, 1961 (Box 842, Folder 22)
    - Sibley's, undated (Box 842, Folder 23)
    - Sidney's, 1989 (Box 842, Folder 24)
    - Sight, 1987-1990 (Box 842, Folder 25)
    - Signals, 1987-1992 (Box 842, Folder 26)
    - Signature, 1979-1986 (Box 842, Folder 26)
    - Silver Burdette, 1986 (Box 842, Folder 27)
    - Simplicity, circa 1980s (Box 842, Folder 28)
    - Singer, 1988 (Box 842, Folder 29)
    - Skateboard World, 1978-1979 (Box 842, Folder 30)
    - Skateboarder, 1979 (Box 842, Folder 31)
    - Skeptic, 1975 (Box 842, Folder 32)
    - Ski, 1987-1993 (Box 842, Folder 33-34)
    - Ski America, 1979-1989 (Box 842, Folder 35)
    - Skillern's, 1962 (Box 842, Folder 36)
    - Ski Utah, 1986-1987 (Box 842, Folder 37)
    - Ski Watch, 1986-1989 (Box 842, Folder 38)
    - Smart, 1990 (Box 842, Folder 39)
    - Smart Business, 2000 (Box 842, Folder 40)
    - Smart Kids, 1991 (Box 842, Folder 41)
    - Smart Money, 2000 (Box 842, Folder 42)
    - Smithsonian Institute, 1967-1988 (Box 842, Folder 43-44)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1998 (Box 843, Folder 1)
    - Smythe & Co., 1991 (Box 843, Folder 2)
    - Snowgoer, 1991 (Box 843, Folder 3)
    - Snowmobile, 1991 (Box 843, Folder 4)
    - Snowshoe, 1989-1990 (Box 843, Folder 5)
    - Soap Opera Digest, 2000 (Box 843, Folder 6)
    - Soap Opera News, 1998 (Box 843, Folder 7)
    - Soap Opera Spectacular, 1995 (Box 843, Folder 8)
    - Soap Opera Update, circa 1980s (Box 843, Folder 9)
    - Soccer Now, 1984-1989 (Box 843, Folder 10)
    - Soccer Score, 1977-1980 (Box 843, Folder 11)
    - Society for Visual Education, 1986-1989 (Box 843, Folder 12)
    - Society Youth, 1999 (Box 843, Folder 13)
    - Software Development, 1997-1999\ (Box 843, Folder 14)
    - Sojourns, 1990 (Box 843, Folder 15)
    - Soldiers, 1986 (Box 843, Folder 16)
    - Soloflex, 1991 (Box 843, Folder 17)
    - Solutions, undated (Box 843, Folder 18)
    - Some's Uniform Catalog, 1986 (Box 843, Folder 19)
    - Somos, 1991-1993 (Box 843, Folder 20)
    - Sorbus Supplies, 1985-1987 (Box 843, Folder 21)
    - Source, 1992 (Box 843, Folder 22)
    - Southern Outdoors, 1981 (Box 843, Folder 23)
    - South Florida, 1995 (Box 843, Folder 24)
    - South Hills Electronics, 1989 (Box 843, Folder 25)
    - South Hills Seaport Museum, circa 1980 (Box 843, Folder 26)
    - South Western Publishing Company, 1986 (Box 843, Folder 27)
    - Southeast Alaska, 1988 (Box 843, Folder 28)
    - Southern California Golf Association, 1989 (Box 843, Folder 29)
    - Southern Links, 1989 (Box 843, Folder 30)
    - Southern Outdoors, 1981 (Box 843, Folder 31)
    - Southwest Sampler, 1990 (Box 843, Folder 32)
    - Southwestern Company, 1966 (Box 843, Folder 33)
    - Spa Finder, 1989-1990 (Box 843, Folder 34)
    - Spectrum Educational Media, 1987 (Box 843, Folder 35)
    - Spencer Gifts, 1990 (Box 843, Folder 36)
    - Spenco Medical Corp., 1985-1986 (Box 843, Folder 37)
    - Sperry & Hutchinson, 1989 (Box 843, Folder 38)
    - Spiegel, 1959-2000 (Box 843, Folder 39-40)
    - Spin, 2000-2001 (Box 844, Folder 1)
    - Spirit of Ninja, 1986 (folder only) (Box 844, Folder 2)
    - Splice, circa 1980s (Box 844, Folder 3)
    - Sport Diver, 2000 (Box 844, Folder 4)
    - Sport Fishing, 1986 (Box 844, Folder 5)
    - Sporting News, 1983 (Box 844, Folder 6)
    - Sports Afield, circa 1980s (Box 844, Folder 7-8)
    - Sports Illustrated, 1981-1996 (Box 844, Folder 9-10)
    - Sports Marketing Group, 1988 (Box 844, Folder 11)
    - Sports Review Wrestling, 1989 (Box 844, Folder 12)
    - Sportwide, 1991 (Box 844, Folder 13)
    - Sporty's Pilot Shop, 1985-1986 (Box 844, Folder 14)
    - St. Louis Cardinals, 1989 (Box 844, Folder 15)
    - Standard, 1951 (Box 844, Folder 16)
    - Standing Ovation, 1990 (Box 844, Folder 17)
    - Stanley Home Products, circa 1970s (Box 844, Folder 18)
    - Staples, 2000 (Box 844, Folder 19)
    - Stark Brothers, 1978 (Box 844, Folder 20)
    - Stereo Discounters Electronic World Inc., 1986 (Box 844, Folder 21)
    - Stereo Review, 1979-1988 (Box 844, Folder 22-24)
    - Storybook Heirlooms, 1991 (Box 844, Folder 25)
    - Stratford Hall, 1986-1991 (Box 844, Folder 26)
    - Strawbridge and Clothier, 1988-1990 (Box 844, Folder 27)
    - Strength Training, 1985 (Box 844, Folder 28)
    - Student Life, 1987-1988 (Box 844, Folder 29)
    - Student Magazine, circa 1980s (Box 844, Folder 30)
    - Stuff, 1998 (Box 844, Folder 31)
    - Stuller Settings, 1986 (Box 844, Folder 32)
    - STV Magazine, 1987 (Box 844, Folder 33-34)
    - Successful Business, 1978 (Box 845, Folder 1)
    - Successful Farming, 1903 (Box 845, Folder 2)
    - Summit University, 1986 (Box 845, Folder 3)
    - Sunbelt Sportswear, 1985-1992 (Box 845, Folder 4-5)
    - Sunburst, 1987-1988 (Box 845, Folder 6)
    - Sundance, 1999 (Box 845, Folder 7)
    - Sunday, 1985 (Box 845, Folder 8)
    - Sunday Land Farms, 1982-1990 (Box 845, Folder 9)
    - Sunset, 1993 (Box 845, Folder 10)
    - Sunset House, 1971-1981 (Box 845, Folder 11-12)
    - Superfit, 1985 (Box 845, Folder 13)
    - Surfer, 1978-1988 (Box 845, Folder 14-19)
    - Surfer Publishing, 1980 (Box 845, Folder 20)
    - Surgery, Gynecology, and Obstetrics, 1955-1987 (Box 845, Folder 21)
    - Surprises, circa 1986 (Box 845, Folder 22)
    - Surveyor Magazine, 1969 (Box 845, Folder 23)
    - S.W.A.T, 1990 (Box 845, Folder 24)
    - Sweden Traveler, 1991 (Box 845, Folder 25)
    - Swimming World, 1983-1991 (Box 845, Folder 26-27)
    - Swimwear Illustrated, 1987 (Box 845, Folder 28)
    - Swiss Colony, 1959-1991 (Box 845, Folder 29)
    - Sycom, 1987-1989 (Box 845, Folder 30-31)
    - Synagogue and Temple, 1962 (Box 845, Folder 32)
    - Tack 'n Togs, 1999 (Box 845, Folder 33)
    - Talbot's, 1996-2000 (Box 846, Folder 1-3)
    - Tandy, 1974-1985 (Box 846, Folder 4)
    - Tandy Crafts, 1980 (Box 846, Folder 5)
    - Tata Chemicals, 1995-1996 (Box 846, Folder 6)
    - Tata Tea Limited, 1995-1996 (Box 846, Folder 7)
    - Technology Illustrated, 1982-1983 (Box 846, Folder 8)
    - Technology Transfer Institute, 1986-1989 (Box 846, Folder 9)
    - Teddy Bear, 1995 (Box 846, Folder 10)
    - Telehealth, 1999 (Box 846, Folder 11)
    - Teleradiology, circa 2000s (Box 846, Folder 12)
    - Television Forecast Inc., 1954 (Box 846, Folder 13)
    - Telva, 1994 (Box 846, Folder 14)
    - Temple University, 1981 (Box 846, Folder 15)
    - Tender Heart Treasury, 1987-1989 (Box 846, Folder 16)
    - Texaco, 1934 (Box 846, Folder 17)
    - Texas Business, 1985-1987 (Box 846, Folder 18)
    - Texas Highways, 1996 (Box 846, Folder 19)
    - Texas Instruments, 1987 (Box 846, Folder 20)
    - Thalhimers, 1991 (Box 846, Folder 21)
    - These Days, 1982-1983 (Box 846, Folder 22)
    - Thomas Computer Corporation, 1987-1990 (Box 846, Folder 23)
    - Thomas Cook, 1995 (Box 846, Folder 24)
    - Thomas Road Baptist Church, 1979-1980 (Box 846, Folder 25)
    - Thos. Oak and Sons, 1989 (Box 846, Folder 26)
    - Tigerbeat, 1986 (Box 846, Folder 27)
    - Tiger Software, circa 1980s (Box 846, Folder 28)
    - Time, 1953-1988 (Box 846, Folder 29-31)
    - Times Mirror Magazines, 1987-1990 (Box 846, Folder 32)
    - Timothy's by Mail, 1986 (Box 846, Folder 33)
    - Tinder Box International, 1987 (Box 846, Folder 34)
    - TJ's Swim and Trophy, 1987-1989 (Box 846, Folder 35)
    - Today's Bride, 1990 (Box 846, Folder 36)
    - Today's Viewpoint, 1976 (Box 846, Folder 37)
    - Tog Shop, 1988 (Box 846, Folder 38)
    - Tomorrow's Comics, 1992 (Box 846, Folder 39)
    - Tonquish Creek, 1990 (Box 846, Folder 40)
    - Tools of the Trade, 1999 (Box 846, Folder 41)
    - Top Gear, 1994 (Box 846, Folder 42-43)
    - Topps, 1990-1992 (Box 846, Folder 44-46)
    - Top Value, 1988-1996 (Box 846, Folder 47)
    - Total Television, circa 1980s (Box 847, Folder 1)
    - Tour Alaska, 1986-1988 (Box 847, Folder 2)
    - Town and Country, 1987-1996 (Box 847, Folder 3-4)
    - Toy's "R" Us, 1990-1996 (Box 847, Folder 5)
    - Traditions, 1990 (Box 847, Folder 6)
    - Trailblazer, 1985-1988 (Box 847, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, 1985 (Box 847, Folder 8)
    - Trailer Boats, 1988-1991 (Box 847, Folder 9-10)
    - Trains, 1983-1985 (Box 847, Folder 11)
    - Transamerica, 1986 (Box 847, Folder 12)
    - TravAlaska, 1987-1988 (Box 847, Folder 13)
    - Traveler, 1987-1988 (Box 847, Folder 14)
    - Trawler Cruiser Yacht, 1982 (Box 847, Folder 15)
    - Treasure Island, 1987 (Box 847, Folder 16)
    - Treasures, 1977 (Box 847, Folder 17)
    - Treasures in Needlework, 1992 (Box 847, Folder 18)
    - The Treehouse, 1979 (Box 847, Folder 19)
    - Triangle Publication, 1985 (Box 847, Folder 20)
    - Trifles, 1989-1987 (Box 847, Folder 21)
    - Trillion, 1987 (Box 847, Folder 22)
    - Truck Prices, 1989-1990 (Box 847, Folder 23)
    - Trucks, 1986-1990 (Box 847, Folder 24)
    - Tupperware, circa 1980s (Box 847, Folder 25)
    - Turner Publishing, circa 1990s (Box 847, Folder 26)
    - TV Guide, 1980-2000 (Box 847, Folder 27-29)
    - TV Guide, 1957-1998 (Box 848, Folder 1-3)
    - TWA, 1975-1982 (Box 848, Folder 4)
    - Tweeds, 1987-1992 (Box 848, Folder 5-6)
    - U-Bild, 1980s (Box 848, Folder 7)
    - U-Haul, circa 1980s (Box 848, Folder 8)
    - UARCO Office Products, 1989 (Box 848, Folder 9)
    - UK/LA 1988 (Box 848, Folder 10)
    - Ultimate Computer Supplies, 1986 (Box 848, Folder 11)
    - Undergear, 1991 (Box 848, Folder 12)
    - Unidad de Diseno y Comunicacion, 1991-1992 (Box 848, Folder 13)
    - Unique Homes, 1984-1991 (Box 848, Folder 14)
    - Unisys, circa 1980s (Box 848, Folder 13)
    - United Airlines, 1977-1990 (Box 848, Folder 14)
    - United Buying Products, 1985-1986 (Box 848, Folder 15)
    - United National Real Estate, 1986-1987 (Box 848, Folder 16)
    - U.S Department of Health and Human Services, 1989 (Box 848, Folder 17)
    - United States Golf Association, 1987 (Box 848, Folder 18)
    - United States Government Printing Office, 1976-1984 (Box 848, Folder 19)
    - United States Naval Institute, 1983-1988 (Box 848, Folder 20-22)
    - United States Power Squadrons, 1981 (Box 848, Folder 23)
    - United Telephone, 1992 (Box 848, Folder 24)
    - University Communications, 1976-1979 (Box 849, Folder 1)
    - University of California- Los Angeles, 1988-1989 (Box 849, Folder 2)
    - University of Chicago, 1990-2001 (Box 849, Folder 3)
    - University of Illinois, 1990-1991 (Box 849, Folder 4)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1986-1987 (Box 849, Folder 5)
    - University Products, 1988-1989 (Box 849, Folder 6)
    - Unix Review, 1994 (Box 849, Folder 7)
    - Upbeat, Inc. circa 1980s (Box 849, Folder 8)
    - Upscale, 1996 (Box 849, Folder 9)
    - US Cavalry, 1985-1988 (Box 849, Folder 10)
    - US News and World Report, 1970-1990 (Box 849, Folder 11-13)
    - Utah!, 1988-1990 (Box 849, Folder 14)
    - V, 1989 (Box 849, Folder 15)
    - Valve World, 1936-1955 (Box 849, Folder 16)
    - Van Dyke's, 1988-1989 (Box 849, Folder 17)
    - Van Kampen Merritt, circa 1980s (Box 849, Folder 18)
    - Van, Pickup, and Off Road World, 1979 (Box 849, Folder 19)
    - Van World, 1978 (Box 849, Folder 20)
    - Vax Profesional, 1985 (Box 849, Folder 21)
    - Vegetarian Times, 1991 (Box 849, Folder 22)
    - Vela Highwind Centers (Box 849, Folder 23)
    - Venture, 1967 (Box 849, Folder 24)
    - Very Thing, 1989 (Box 849, Folder 25)
    - Vette, 1989-1990 (Box 849, Folder 26)
    - Vibe, 2000 (Box 849, Folder 27)
    - Victoria and Albert Museum, 1995 (Box 849, Folder 28)
    - Video Times, 1990 (Box 849, Folder 29)
    - Viking Penguin, 1987 (Box 849, Folder 30)
    - Virtual Reality, 1994 (Box 849, Folder 31)
    - Visa, 1979-1986 (Box 849, Folder 32)
    - Vision, 1944 (Box 849, Folder 33)
    - Vision Works, 1989 (Box 849, Folder 34)
    - Vista, 1990 (Box 850, Folder 1)
    - Vital, 1978 (Box 850, Folder 2)
    - Viva, 1996 (Box 850, Folder 3)
    - Vogue, 1970-1993 (Box 850, Folder 4-7)
    - Vogue Knitting, 1982-1993 (Box 850, Folder 8)
    - VW Action, 1984 (Box 850, Folder 9)
    - W, 1986-1987 (Box 850, Folder 10)
    - Waccamaw Pottery, circa 1990s (Box 850, Folder 11)
    - WA Case and Sons, 1954 (Box 850, Folder 12)
    - Wadsworth Publishing Company, 1976 (Box 850, Folder 13)
    - Wahl Investments, 1986-1987 (Box 850, Folder 14)
    - Wal-Mart, 1986 (Box 850, Folder 15)
    - Walgreen's, 1990 (Box 850, Folder 16)
    - Walt Disney Company, 1980-1991 (Box 850, Folder 17)
    - Walter Drake, 1982 (Box 850, Folder 18)
    - Walter's, 1988 (Box 850, Folder 19)
    - Wang, 1984-1989 (Box 850, Folder 20)
    - Warn Industries, 1987-1988 (Box 850, Folder 21)
    - Water Ski, 1985-1991 (Box 850, Folder 22-24)
    - Waterbed City, 1980s (Box 850, Folder 25)
    - Waterbed Gallery, circa 1980s (Box 850, Folder 26)
    - Wayside Gardens, 1985-1991 (Box 850, Folder 27)
    - WB, 1988 (Box 850, Folder 28)
    - W. Bell and Co., 1986 (Box 850, Folder 29)
    - WE, 1994 (Box 850, Folder 30)
    - Wear-Guard, 1986 (Box 850, Folder 31)
    - Wearhouse Imprinted Sportswear, 1988-1990 (Box 850, Folder 32)
    - Webster's, 1961 (Box 850, Folder 33)
    - Wedding Dresses and Bridal Party Magazine, 1991 (Box 850, Folder 34)
    - Wedding Registry, circa 1980s (Box 850, Folder 35)
    - Wegman's Food Markets, 1990 (Box 850, Folder 36)
    - Weight Watchers, 1988-1994 (Box 850, Folder 37-38)
    - Weight Watchers, 1979-1985 (Box 851, Folder 1-2)
    - Weinstocks, 1988-1989 (Box 851, Folder 3)
    - Welsh Dragon, 1986 (Box 851, Folder 4)
    - West Bend, 1970 (Box 851, Folder 5)
    - West Hollywood Magazine, circa 1990s (Box 851, Folder 6)
    - West Marine Products, 1987 (Box 851, Folder 7)
    - Western Auto, 1959-1971 (Box 851, Folder 8)
    - Western Iron Stores, 1954 (Box 851, Folder 9)
    - Western Union, 1986-1987 (Box 851, Folder 10)
    - Westinghouse, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 851, Folder 11)
    - Westminister Press, 1948 (Box 851, Folder 12)
    - Westways, 1981 (Box 851, Folder 13)
    - W.F. McLaughlin Co., 1904 (Box 851, Folder 14)
    - Where, 1999-2000 (Box 851, Folder 15)
    - White House, 1986 (Box 851, Folder 16)
    - Whites, 1963-circa 1980 (Box 851, Folder 17)
    - Wiser Educational, 1986 (Box 851, Folder 18)
    - Wildlife Conservation, 1992 (Box 851, Folder 19)
    - Wildseed Farms, 1988 (Box 851, Folder 20)
    - Williams-Sanoma, 1990-1999 (Box 851, Folder 21)
    - Willow Ridge, 1990 (Box 851, Folder 22)
    - Wilson, 1973-1985 (Box 851, Folder 23)
    - Wilson's, 1983 (Box 851, Folder 24)
    - Wilton Communications, 1985-1988 (Box 851, Folder 25)
    - Wilton Enterprises, 1979- circa 1980s (Box 851, Folder 26-27)
    - Winchester, 1969-1990 (Box 851, Folder 28)
    - Windham Hill Productions, 1989 (Box 851, Folder 29)
    - Windows NT Systems, 1999 (Box 851, Folder 30)
    - Wind Rider, 1982-1987 (Box 851, Folder 31)
    - Windsor Vineyards, 1986 (Box 851, Folder 32)
    - Wind Surf, 1982-1984 (Box 851, Folder 33-34)
    - Women's Health, 1999 (Box 852, Folder 1)
    - Woman's Sports and Fitness, 1988-1984 (Box 852, Folder 2)
    - Wood, 1994 (Box 852, Folder 3)
    - Wood Producers Publications, 1978-1980 (Box 852, Folder 4)
    - Wood Technology, 1999 (Box 852, Folder 5)
    - Woodward & Lothrop, 1980 (Box 852, Folder 6)
    - Woolson Spice Co., 1953 (Box 852, Folder 7)
    - Woolworth, 1979 (Box 852, Folder 8)
    - Worldstyle, 1988 (Box 852, Folder 9)
    - Working Woman, 1976-1983 (Box 852, Folder 10)
    - World Airways, 1988 (Box 852, Folder 11)
    - World Boxing, 1993 (Box 852, Folder 12)
    - World Cup Soccer, 1994 (Box 852, Folder 13-14)
    - World Monitor, 1990 (Box 852, Folder 15)
    - World Water Skiing, 1979-1984 (Box 852, Folder 16-17)
    - World Wildlife Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 852, Folder 18)
    - World Wrestling Federation, 1985-1989 (Box 852, Folder 19-20)
    - Worldwide Challenge, 1986-1989 (Box 852, Folder 21)
    - Wrestle America, 1992 (Box 852, Folder 22)
    - Wrestling Eye, 1988-1989 (Box 852, Folder 23)
    - Wrestling Fury (Box 852, Folder 24)
    - Wright Line, 1987-1989 (Box 852, Folder 25)
    - WSB-TV, 1989 (Box 852, Folder 26)
    - WTW, 1987-1990 (Box 852, Folder 27)
    - WTVS, 1988 (Box 852, Folder 28)
    - Xerox, 1980-1989 (Box 852, Folder 29)
    - Yachting, 1940-1989 (Box 852, Folder 30-31)
    - Yahoo!, 2000 (Box 852, Folder 32)
    - Yankee, 1987 (Box 852, Folder 33)
    - Yield House, 1986-1992 (Box 852, Folder 34)
    - Yo, 1999 (Box 852, Folder 35)
    - Younkers, circa 1980s (Box 852, Folder 36)
    - Your Prom, 1990 (Box 852, Folder 37)
    - Zale's, 1962-1968 (Box 852, Folder 38)
    - Zandervan, 1986-1988 (Box 852, Folder 39)
    - Zayre, 1988 (Box 852, Folder 40)
    - Zenith, 1964-1969 (Box 852, Folder 41)
    - Zenith Aviation Books, 1988 (Box 852, Folder 42)
    - Zesco Products, 1986-1992 (Box 852, Folder 43)
    - Zoo Life, 1991 (Box 852, Folder 44)
    - Zotos International, 1988 (Box 852, Folder 45)
  - Subseries 2: Books
    - Andrews McMeel Publishing, A Treasury of Friendship, 2000 (Box 853, Folder 1)
    - Andrews McMeel Publishing, Hugs, Especially for Sisters, 2000 (Box 853, Folder 2)
    - Andrews McMeel Publishing, The Way We Were, 1973 (Box 853, Folder 3)
    - Award Publications Limited, Cathy Dress Up Press-Out Doll, 1972 (Box 853, Folder 4)
    - Badaracco, Claire, American Culture and the Marketplace, 1992 (Box 853, Folder 5-7)
    - Berry, Carmen Rennee and Tamara Traeder, Women's Rites, Girlfriends' Rituals, 1998 (Box 853, Folder 8)
    - Bottomer, Paul, Salsa!, 1996 (Box 853, Folder 9)
    - Butterick, 101 Crafts Under $10, 2000 (Box 853, Folder 10)
    - Carlson, Richard, A Don't Sweat the Small Stuff Treasury, 2000 (Box 853, Folder 11)
    - Cornwell, Patricia, The Last Precinct, 2000 (Box 853, Folder 12)
    - Drudge, Matt, Drudge Manifesto, 2000 (Box 853, Folder 13)
    - Exley, Helen, A Special Collection in Praise of Mothers, 1995 (Box 853, Folder 14)
    - Exley, Helen, Cats, 1995 (Box 853, Folder 15)
    - Exley, Helen, Over Vriendschap, 2000 (Box 853, Folder 16)
    - Exley, Helen, To My Daughter with Love, 1994 (Box 853, Folder 17)
    - Exley, Helen, Wisdom of the Millennium, 2000 (Box 853, Folder 18)
    - Exley, Helen, Words of Wisdom, 1997 (Box 853, Folder 19)
    - Fulton, Jennifer, The Complete Idiot's Guide to DOS, 1994 (Box 854, Folder 1)
    - Glencoe, Earth Science, 1994 (Box 854, Folder 2)
    - Glencoe, Literature – Reader's Choice, 2000 (Box 854, Folder 3)
    - Glencoe, Pre-Algebra – An Integrated Transition to Algebra and Geometry, 2001 (Box 854, Folder 4)
    - Glencoe, Writer's Choice – Grammar and Composition, 1996 (Box 854, Folder 5)
    - Goldstein, Bobbye S., Inner Chimes – Poems on Poetry, 1992 (Box 854, Folder 6)
    - Hart, John, 50 Portrait Lighting Techniques for Pictures that Sell, 1995 (Box 854, Folder 7)
    - Honor Books, God's Little Christmas Book, 1999 (Box 854, Folder 8)
    - Honor Books, God's Little Instruction Book, 1999 (Box 854, Folder 9)
    - IBM, 16X Max DVD-ROM Drive, User's Guide, 2000 (Box 854, Folder 10)